You.
You... you're the
head coach, is that...
Is that what
you're saying?
Oh,
come on,
your lies are getting
more and
more ridiculous.
You're the head coach
of the... of the Knights?
Allen.
Tell me he's
making it up.
I'm just a
security manager.
I don't have
access to the field,
let alone the execs or the head coach.
Hell, how would I even know he's lying or not?
He's just trying
to act a big shot
to make us forget
that he's broke.
Yeah.
This loser
would never
be a head coach.
Yeah,
a loser like him
could never run a
team like the Knights.
If I didn't work
for the Knights,
I might have
believed you, Ted.
Nice try, by the way.
You're no head coach.
You're just a fraud
in cheap clothes.
So,
all of you
think that I'm lying?
A head coach
dressed like that?
Next time you want
to try playing rich,
at least get yourself
a new suit first.
Hello and
welcome everyone.
Welcome to the place.
Please take a
look at our menu.
-Thank you.
-It's okay, I promise.
Our shrimp scampi with broccolini is too...
Oh, Jesus.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is that Coach Ted,
the head coach
of the Knights?